Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Slides, 1974-1987, Series 8:; (Boxes 16-18; 3 linear feet)
  - Artist Files: H. Schneiderman (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Seth Seiderman (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Alan Sonneman (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Susan Stella (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Al Stone (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Janet Tholen (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Jerry Wellman (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Peter Zokofsky (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Unknown Artists (Box 18)
  - Journal #33, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Journal #42, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Journal #47, 1987 (Box 18)